http://www.ebmpapst.us/en/company/policy/privacy_policy/privacy_policy_1.html

Contact
North American Region (NAR)
Privacy policy
ebm-papst Inc., is sensitive to privacy issues concerning the use of information provided over the internet, and we understand the importance of protecting any personal information you may provide to us through the use of this website.
You are not required to register or provide information to us in order to visit this website. To obtain information, services, or products via this website, or to allow ebm-papst to respond to your requests for information, you may be asked to voluntarily provide non-public, personal information. Examples of personal information might include your name, address, or telephone number. We use your information to provide the information, products, or services you requested and to enhance your use of this website. ebm-papst Inc. is the owner of the information collected on this site, and we do not sell or rent your name or private information to third parties. Private information may be disclosed if required by a court order, statute, law, or regulation.Our webserver collects general information that does not relate to specific individual visitors, such as the number of visits to this website, the number of pages viewed, and the domains from which people visit this web site.You acknowledge that acceptance of this privacy policy, as updated from time to time at this location, is a condition to your use of our web site and you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions.To unsubscribe from future email communications, please click here:
https://info.ebmpapst.us/unsubscribe
Print
Sitemap
Recommend this page
Bookmark this page
Products |
Markets |
GreenTech |
